hosterpk.com 2014-06-30

# HosterPK | Privacy Policy

##  New ASP.NET 4.5, 4.0, 3.5 Hosting, with AJAX / Silverlight

##  New MS Sql Server 2008 available, along with Sql Server 2005 

##  Quick & Easy Payment Methods Pay easily and conveniently using Bank Deposit, ATM Transfer, Internet Banking in your _nearest Bank Alfalah, Standard Chartered, Silkbank branches_. **EasyPaisa payments** are also supported. 

**Want to make payment through Credit Card?** Now you can pay using your Visa, Master, American Express Cards and Paypal as well. For more details click here. 

##  **Web hosting with free .com, .net, .org domains**

##  Setup charges waived for all packages 

##  ASP.NET, PHP plans as low as Rs. 1400 (17.50) / yr 

##  _Instant account activation_

Our Hosting Platform

  *   
Windows 2008 R2 
  *   
CloudLinux OS
  *   
Apache Web Server 
  *   
Litespeed Web Server 
  *    
ASP.NET 4.5, 4.0, 3.5, 2.0, 1.1 Hosting 
  *   
Silverlight Hosting 
  *    
AJAX, MVC, LINQ Supported 
  *    
PHP 4, 5 Hosting 
  *    
SQL Server 2008 Hosting
  *   
SQL Server 2005 
  *    
MySql Server Hosting
  *    
Wordpress Hosting 
  *    
Joomla Hosting 
  *    
Drupal Hosting 

|  |  HosterPK's Privacy Policy   
---  
  
**Protecting your privacy is critical to HosterPK. We will not sell, lease or exchange your personal data to third parties without first obtaining your express consent.**

This Privacy Policy describes how HosterPK collects information from all end users (website visitors, members, and hosting service users), and what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors have concerning the collection and use of such information. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. 

Personal Information HosterPK Collects and How It Is Used   
  
_**Why We Collect Information**_

HosterPK collects information in different ways from Visitors who access the various parts of our Website, or use our Services, and subscribers (members). We use this information to provide a customized experience as you use our Services. We also collect technical information such as IP addresses and the date and time of visits. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Web site. We also use it to identify and protect us against malicious hackers or abusers.   
  
_**What We do With This Information**_   
HosterPK will not sell or give any personal information regarding its visitors or service users to any third party. Any information that you give to us is held with the utmost care and security. Generally, we do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.   
_**Responses to Email Inquiries**_   
When Visitors send email inquiries to HosterPK, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. HosterPK does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.   
_**Special Cases**_   
It is HosterPK policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors. However, HosterPK may disclose personal information about Visitors, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web site accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone, or to protect HosterPK.   
_**"Cookies" and How HosterPK Uses Them**_   
A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. HosterPK may use cookies to store and collect information, which is needed for HosterPK to work properly. We also may use cookies to track information for statistical purposes to improve the services we provide. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Advertisers and partners (like Google) may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.   
_**HosterPK Commitment to Data Security**_   
Services and Web sites we sponsor or host have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.   
_**Revisions to This Policy** _   
HosterPK reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. 

Terms of Service. Please also see our Terms Of Service, which describes the use, disclaimers, indemnification and limitation of liability governing the use of the entire HosterPK web site.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please visit the Contact Us page.
